In the last section,
在上一章
you used a custom transformer that extracted whether each text started with a verb.
你使用了一个自定义的转换器用来提取特征 即每条文本是不是以动词开头
You can implement a custom transformer
你可以通过拓展 scikit-learn 的基类
yourself by extending the base class in scikit-learn.
自己实现一个转换器
Here is a very simple example that multiplies the input data by ten.
这有一个非常简单的例子 将输入数据乘以 10
Remember, all estimators need
记住所有评估器需要
a fit method to learn on the data and because this is a transformer,
一个 fit 方法来接收数据进行学习 并且因为这是一个转换器
we'll need a transform method.
你还需要一个 transform 方法
The transform method is where will include the code that will transforms the data.
transform 方法中要包含转换数据的代码
Note that both fit and transform,
注意 fit 和 transform 方法
typically take a 2D array X.
通常接收一个 2D 数组 X
Next, we'll create a custom transformer that has a bit more significance.
接下来 我们创建一个更有实用意义的转换器
Here is a case normalizer which simply converts all text to lowercase.
这是一个大小写转换器 (case normalizer) 简单地将所有文本转成小写
We aren't setting anything in our init method,
在 init 方法中 我们不做任何设置
so we can actually remove that.
所以我们其实可以不要它
We can leave our fit method as is and focus on the transform method.
保留 fit 方法不变 来看 transform 方法
We can lowercase all the values in X by
我们可以使用 lambda 函数
applying a lambda function that occurs lower on each value.
a将 X 中的所有值转成小写
We'll have to wrap this in a panda series to be able to use a Pi function and
我们需要将这个包装成 pandas 序列 (Series) 以便使用 apply 函数
lastly we'll put dot values at the end to to convert it back to a NumPy array.
最后加上 .values 将它转换为 NumPy 数组 (array)
Awesome. It's a good idea to learn how to write your own custom functions.
很棒编写自己的函数是个很好的想法
It allows you to have more control and flexibility with your machine learning pipelines.
让你可以更好更灵活地控制自己的机器学习管道
Another way to create custom transformers is by using
另一种创建自己的转换器的方法是使用
this function transformer from scikit-learn preprocessing module.
scikit-learn 库 preprocessing 模块的transformer 函数
This allows you to wrap an existing function
这类方法可以打包一个已有的
including one that you write to become a transformer.
或自定义的函数作为转换器
This allows less flexibility,
这种方法的灵活性稍差
but it is pretty simple.
但很简单
You can learn more about this in the link below.
你可以参考下面的链接了解更多